Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU), Hudson Valley Area Joint Board; Records apap050
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU), Hudson Valley Area Joint Board Records
1919-1990
Undated
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
apap050
13.23 cubic ft.
The Hudson Valley Area Joint Board was formed in 1957 through the merger of the Columbia County and Mid-Hudson Valley Joint Boards. At that point, the two joint boards were affiliated of the Textile Workers Union of America (TWUA), which merged with the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America (ACWA) in 1976 to form the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU). The collection documents the organization, administration, and activities of the Hudson Valley Area Joint Board and its predecessor organizations.
Administrative History
The Hudson Valley Area Joint Board was formed in 1957 through the merger of the Columbia County and Mid-Hudson Valley Joint Boards. At this point, the two joint boards were affiliated of the Textile Workers Union of America (TWUA), which merged with the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America (ACWA) in 1976 to form the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU). After the formation of the Hudson Valley Area Joint Board in 1957, other joint boards joined the union. The Capital District Joint Board, which was chartered in 1937, joined the Hudson Valley Area Joint Board in 1968. The Amsterdam Joint Board, which was charted in 1942, also joined the Hudson Valley Area Joint Board in the mid 1960's. All of the joint boards had local chapters that represented different workplaces and institutions. Each local chapter had its own set of bylaws and constitutions, and each institution had its own set of bylaws and constitutions as well.
Prior to the merge the Capital District Joint Board oversaw the Berkshire Joint Board, which was chartered in 1946. When the merge occurred, the Hudson Valley Area Joint Board oversaw their records until 1968-1969. The Berkshire Joint Board then joined the Connecticut Joint Board in 1969. The Capital District Area Joint Board was also affiliated with the Troy Area Industrial Union Council, CIO. The Hudson Valley Area Joint Board was also associated with the AFL-CIO and helped keep track of their local unions. These unions included the Upper Hudson Area Industrial Council, which became the Upper Hudson Area Central Labor Union in 1958. These records were held by the Columbia County Joint Board until the merge. The Hudson Valley Area Joint Board also helped maintain the Central Labor Union of New York records as well.
Arrangement
This collection is made up of five series. Series 1 includes records documenting the activities of the Hudson Valley Area Joint Board. Series 2 documents the activities relating to the Amsterdam Joint Board. Series 3 includes records from the Capital District Area Joint Board. Series 4 is made up of records relating to the Columbia County Joint Board and Series 5 contains records relating to the Mid-Hudson Valley Area Joint Board.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
All the items in series 1 of this manuscript group were lent to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives, by the Hudson Valley Area Joint Board, ACTWU, and were subsequently microfilmed as a part of the Harry Van Arsdale, Jr., Labor History Project. The originals have been returned to the Hudson Valley Area Joint Board. The original items in series 2-5 were subsequently donated.
Access
Access to this collection is unrestricted.
Scope and Contents
This collection divided into five series that document the organization, administration and activities of the Hudson Valley Area Joint Board of the ACTWU and its predecessor organizations. The collection contains meeting minutes, correspondence, contracts and arbitration documents, board by-laws and organizing leaflets for the Hudson Valley Board and its predecessors. The collection also contains bylaws, constitutions, and meeting minutes of the AFL-CIO organizations that the Hudson Valley Area Joint Board helped maintain.
Indexes to Companies Where Locals Worked
Below is a list of the different local chapters of the joint boards prior to their merge. The Hudson Valley Area Joint Board contains all of the local chapters after the merge, as well as the Berkshire Joint Board local records as well.
Amsterdam Joint Board (chartered 1942; merged with the Hudson Valley Area Joint Board ca. 1965) Bigelow-Sanford Carpet Company (Local 1) Mohasco Industries (Local 489) Mohawk Carpet Mills (Local 489 and Local 856) Fownes Brothers and Company, Inc. (Locals 646) Chalmers Knitting Company (Local 835) Montco Manufacturing Company, Inc. (Local 835) Local 846 BAM Industries, Inc. (Local 1761)
Capital District Joint Board (chartered, 1937; merged with Hudson Valley Area Joint Board, 1968) Beaunit Mills (Local 89) NAFI Corporation (Local 237) National Automotive Fibres, Inc., NAFI (Local 237) National Automotive Wadding Co., Inc. (Local 237) Waterford Industries (Local 237) Peerless Fibre Company (Local 238 and Garnett Workers Union, Local 577) Cohoes Screen Print Corporation (Local 346) Cohoes Textile Printing Company (Local 346) Wilson Athletic Goods Manufacturing Company, Inc. (Local 574) Cohoes Dyeing and Finishing Company, Inc. (Local 575) Batt and Shoddy Manufacturers (Garnett Workers Union, Local 577) Enterprise Garnetting Co. (Garnett Workers Union, Local 577) Lowenthal and Co. (Garnett Workers Union, Local 577) National Textile Manufacturing Co. (Garnett Workers Union, Local 577) Star Woolen Company (Local 1351 and Garnett Workers Union, Local 577) United Waste Manufacturing Co. (Garnett Workers Union, Local 577) Wilson Brothers, Inc. (Local 675) William Barnet and Son, Inc. (Local 964 and United Textile Workers of America, Local 520) Regis Textiles (Local 907) Albany Parlor Company (Local 976) Montague Furniture Company (Local 976) Montague Upholstering Company (Local 976) Star Textile and Research (Local 1351)
Columbia County Joint Board (existed at least since 1947; merged with the Mid-Hudson Joint Board in 1957 to form the Hudson Valley Area Joint Board) Local 96 Local 791 High Rock Mills, Inc. (Local 792) Springdale Mills (Local 793) Imperial Pen and Pencil Co. (Local 938) Nassau Pen Manufacturing Co. (Local 938) Faith Mills, Inc. (Local 1122) Hudson Glue Corporation (Local 1246) Union Piece Dye Works (Local 1342)
Mid-Hudson Valley Joint Board (chartered 1948; merged with the Columbia County Joint Board in 1957 to form the Hudson Valley Area Joint Board) Braendly Dye Works, Inc. (United Textile Workers of America, Local 282) Capitol Piece Dye Works, Inc. (Local 464) Elk Piece Dye Works, Inc. (Local 464) Garnerville Dye Works, Inc. (Local 464) Poughkeepsie Finishing Corporation (Local 501) Dutchess-Lockwood Holdings (Local 673) Dutchess-Lockwood, Inc. (Local 673) P-V-M Corporation (Local 673) United Wire Goods (Local 683) Textile By-Products (Local 791) Bernhard Altmann International Corp., High Rock Div. (Local 792) High Rock Knitting Corporation (Local 792) High Rock Mills (Local 792) Springdale Mills (Local 793) Local 893 S. Stroock and Company, Inc. (Local 898) Local 982 Tex Ray Fabrics, Inc. (Local 988) Steinfeld Fabrics Company, Inc. (Local 1001) Highland Prints, Inc. (Local 1121) Winston Prints, Inc. (Local 1121) Faith Mills, Inc. (Local 1122) Local 1277 Metrotex, Inc. (Local 1318) Price Fire and Waterproofing Company (Local 1318) Atlas Fibres Company, Inc. (Local 1338) Local 1818 Local 1420
Hudson Valley Area Joint Board (formed in 1957 from the merger of the Columbia County and the Mid-Hudson Joint Boards, TWUA) The Berkshire Joint Board Local Chapters are also listed here.
A. D. Julliard (Local 96) Hightstown Rug Co. (Local 200) Baldwin NAFI Division of Chris-Craft (Local 237) Chris-Craft (Local 237) NAFI Division of Chris Craft (Local 237) Cohoes Fabric Printers (Local 346) E and S Finishing Corporation (Local 464) Elk Piece Dye Works (Local 464) Piermont Sales Corporation (Local 464) SD Sales Corporation (Local 464) Mohasco Corporation (Local 489) Mohawk Carpet Mills (Local 489) Fownes Brothers (Local 646) Label Products Corporation (Local 683) Modern Dust Bag Company, Inc. (Local 683) Modern Filters, Inc. (Local 683) Rockland Knitting Company (Local 683) Lorbrook Corporation (Local 791) Textile By-Products Company, Inc. (Local 791) Bernhard Altman International Corporation (Local 792) High Rock Mills (Local 792) Philmont Finishing Corporation (Local 792) Zamax Manufacturing Company (Local 683) Berkshire - Dewey and Almy Chemical Division of W. R. Grace and Co. (Local 841) Berkshire - W. R Grace and Co.--Dewey and Almy Chemical Division (Local 841) French-American-British Woolens Corp. (Local 898) S. Stroock and Company, Inc. (Local 898) William Barnet and Son, Inc. (Local 964) Albany Parlor Company (Local 976) House of Montague (Local 976) Montague Upholstering Company (Local 976) Star Textile and Research (Local 976) Garnerville Holding Company (Local 982) I.M.I. Warp Knits, Inc. (Local 1001) Leewin Fabrics (Local 1001) Steinfeld Fabrics Company (Local 1001) Blouses by Vera (Local 1032) Prince High Rock Mills, Inc. (Local 1032) Prince Mills, Inc. (Local 1032) Printex Corporation (Local 1032) Elite Manufacturing Company (Local 1122) Elite Yarn Corporation (Local 1122) Faith Mills, Inc. (Local 1122) Hudson Glue Corporation (Local 1246) Hudson Industries Corporation (Local 1246) Insl-X (Local 1277) Berkshire - James Hunter Machine Company (Local 1280) Steiner and Company (Local 1351) Lynrus Company (Local 1318) Metrotex, Inc. (Local 1318) Atlas Fibers (Local 1338) Mastercraft Industries (Local 1338) Skydyne, Inc. (Local 1410 and Federal Labor Union No. 24087, AFL) Jack Barnett and Sons (Local 1420) Jack Barnett Slipper Company (Local 1420) Roselle Shoe Corporation (Local 1420) A and W Products Co., Inc. (Local 1456) Crown Carton (Local 1466) Maybern Corporation (Local 1466) Vaucanson Silk Mills (Local 1477) Ace Fibers Company (Local 1537) Ace Fibre Mills, Inc. (Local 1537) Go-Bar Footwear Company (Local 1537) Inflated Products Contract (Local 1596) Change-O-Matic Corporation (Local 1625) International Cord and Thread Corporation (Local 1625) Carnegie Coating Company (Local 1648) Carnegie Industries (Local 1648) K and P Enterprises, Inc., T/A Carnegie Industries (Local 1648) T/A Carnegie Industries (Local 1648) Sealy of Eastern New York, Inc. (Local 1714) BAM Industries (Local 1761) Beaver Cloth Cutting Machines, Inc. (Local 1761) Academic Press (Local 1870) Johnson Reprint Corporation (Local 1870) Futura Fabrics Corp. (Local 1873) Cryogenic Structures, Inc. (Local 1916) Fasco Coated Products (Local 1939) Packaging Lithographers Division, Packaging Systems Corp. (Local 1939) Packaging Systems Corporation (Local 1939) Ogden Allied Industrial Service Corporation (Local 1939-O) X-Tyal International Corporation (Local 1946) Cohoes Sleeping Bag Factory/Sander Consumer Product Corporation Local 2317) Mohawk and Hudson River Humane Society, Inc. (Local 2317) Sander Consumer Products Corporation (Local 2317) Universal Needle Craft Corporation (Local 2317) Hoerner Waldorf Bag Co. (Local 2318) Industrial Knitted Fabrics & Finishing Corporation (Local 2325) Keuffel and Esser Company (Local 2342) Berkshire Hathaway, Inc. (Local Unknown) Lion Brand, Inc. (Stottville Independent Union)
Labor unions -- New York (State); Labor; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Hudson Valley Joint Board.
- Hudson Valley Area Joint Board, 1919-1989; 8.19 cubic ft.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains records related to the Hudson Valley Area Joint Board. This series is divided into four sub-series. The first sub-series contains the subjetc files of the Joint Board. The second sub-series contains records relating to the Textile Workers Union of America (TWUA), also known as the Amalgamated Clothing and Textiles Workers Union (ACTWU). The third sub-series cotnains local chapter files and the fourth sub-series is contains records associated with the union councils of the AFL-CIO.
  - Subject Files, 1947-1989; Undated; 1.59 cubic ft.
    This sub-series is arranged alphabetically.
    This sub-series contains the subject files of the Hudson Valley Area Joint Board. Included in the subject files are records relating to the organization of the Board, arbitration documents, contracts, correspondence, meeting minutes, and bylaws and constitutions. This series also contains records relating to the Berkshire Joint Board, which the Hudson Valley Area Joint Board oversaw until it left in 1969 to join the Conneticut Joint Board. This series also contains buttons that were worn by the union members to show political support.
    - Amsterdam Joint Board, 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Berkshire Hathaway Inc., 1959 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Berkshire Joint Board, Bylaws, ca. 1960 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Berkshire Joint Board, Charter, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Berkshire Joint Board, Correspondence, 1968-1969; 1971 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Berkshire Joint Board, Local 841, W.R. Grace and Co, Bylaws, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Berkshire Joint Board, Local 1280, Contracts, 1952; 1956; 1958-1959; 1963 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Berkshire Joint Board, Minutes, 1960-1966 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Berkshire Joint Board, By-Laws, ca. 1957; 1958; 1960; 1962; 1967 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Constitution, Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Constitutions of TWUA, 1958; 1962; 1964 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - COPE, Education Conference Russell Sage College, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1961-1964; 1968; 1971 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Dairy Farmers Division, 1986 April-August (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Executive Board Meeting Minutes (1 of 3), 1958-1989 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Executive Board Meeting Minutes (2 of 3), 1958-1989 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Executive Board Meeting Minutes (3 of 3), 1958-1989 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Federation of Textile Representatives, 1965-1967 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - James Thompson Co., Strike, 1950-1953 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Labor and Our Economy (Presentation by Sy Cohen), 1965 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Hudson Valley Area Joint Board Meeting Minutes (1 of 2), 1957-1969; 1984 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Hudson Valley Area Joint Board Meeting Minutes (2 of 2), 1957-1969; 1984 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Monthly Reports, 1958-1961; 1963 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - News Clippings, 1959-1962; 1968-1969; 1971; 1986-1989; Undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Officers of Local and the Joint Board, ca. 1957; 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Organizing File, A&W Products, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Organizing File, Academic Press & Johnson Reprint Employees, Independent Union, ca. 1971 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Organizing File, Airlite Mfg. Co., 1966 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Organizing File, American Felt Company, 1956-1957; 1959-1960; 1962; 1967 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Organizing File, Frost White and Park Tissue, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Organizing File, Johnson & Johnson, Autograph Brush, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Organizing File, Lion Brand, Inc., Stottville Independent Union, 1957-1958; 1961 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Organizing File, Lion Brand, Inc., 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Organizing File, Local #1420, Jack Barnett Slipper Co., 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Organizing File, Local #2318, Hoerner Waldorf Bag, Co., 1978 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Organizing File, Universal Match Co., 1956; 1958; 1960; 1968; 1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Organizing File, Warp Knit, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Organizing Leaflets (1 of 2), 1967-1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Organizing Leaflets (2 of 2), 1967-1971 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Political and Labor Buttons, Undated (Oversized 1)
    - Union National Bank, Hearings, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Textile Workers Union of America (TWUA), 1938-1976; Undated; .6 cubic ft.
    This sub-series contains records relating to the Textile Workers Union of America (TWUA). When the Hudson Valley Area Joint Board was formed in 1957 through the merger of the Columbia County and Mid-Hudson Valley Joint Boards, it was already affiliated with the Textile Workers Union of America (TWUA). The TWUA merged with the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America (ACWA) in 1976 to form the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU). This series contains the records of the assistant state director of the TWUA, as well as the international representation files of the union.
    - Arlington Plastics (Local 1688), Contract Negotiations, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Columbian Rope Workers (Local 1085), Contract Negotiations, 1972; 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Divine Brothers Company (Local 653), Contract Negotiations, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Dunlop Company (Local 150), 1970; 1972; 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Horrocks & Ibbotson (Local 41), Contract Negotiations, 1938-1975 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Fonda Glove Lining (Local 330), Correspondence, 1955-1958 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Fonda Glove Lining (Local 330), NLRB Hearings, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Indian Head Knits, Organizing Files, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Magnetic Lab, B.C. Plastic Division, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Mohawk Brush, Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Mohawk Brush, Meeting Notice, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Palatine Dyeing, Organizing Files, 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Pamphlets, 1960; Undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Triangle Finishing Corp. Newspaper Clippings on Strike, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Triangle Finishing Corporation, Organizing Files, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Unorganized Plants in Utica Area, 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Utica Joint Board Constitution, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Van Raalte Co., Organizing File, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Welfare Plan, 1962-1963; 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Local Files, 1950-1990; Undated; 5.4 cubic ft.
    This sub-series contains the records of the local chapters of the Hudson Valley Area Joint Board. Each local chapter had their own set of records. These records include arbitration documents, bylaws, contracts, and meeting minutes.
    - Local 132-98, Plastic and Metal Products Manufacturers Ass. Agreement, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Local 237, Chris-Craft, By-Laws, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Local 237, Chris-Craft Ind., Contracts, 1963-1982 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Local 237, Chris-Craft, Minutes, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Local 346, Cohoes Fabric Printers, By-Laws, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Local 346, Cohoes Fabric Printers, Contracts, 1965; 1968; 1972; 1974; 1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Local 427, Coated Products Corporation, Division of Essex Chemical Corp., Agreement, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Local 464, E&S Finishing Arbitration, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Local 464, E&S Finishing, Contracts, 1961; 1966; 1971 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Local 464, Elk Piece and Dye Works Arbitration, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Local 464, Elk Piece and Dye Works, Contacts, 1961-1978 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Local 464, Pierment Sales Corp., Contracts, 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Local 464, S.D. Corp., Contracts, 1961-1962; 1966; 1969; 1974 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Local 489, Mohasco Corp., Contracts, 1976; 1979; 1982-1983; 1985 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Local 489, Mohawk Carpet Mills, Contracts, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Local 646, Fownes Brothers, By-laws, ca. 1965; 1977 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Local 646, Fownes Bros. & Co., Inc., Contracts, 1959-1988 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Local 673, P.V.M. Corp., Arbitration, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Local 683, Airlite Mfg. Co., Contracts, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Local 683, By-Laws, 1976-1977; ca. 1978 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Local 683, Label Products Corp, Contracts, 1962; 1964; 1966; 1969 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Local 683, Modern Dust Bag Co., Inc., Contracts, 1962-1967; 1969; 1973; 1976; 1979 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Local 683, Modern Dust Bag, Minutes, Undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Local 683, Modern Filters Inc, Contracts, 1979; 1983 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Local 683, Rockland Knitting Co., Contracts, 1965; 1967; 1969; 1971 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Local 683, Rockland Knitting Co., Correspondence, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Local 683, Zamax Manufacturing Co., Contracts, 1964-1965; 1967; 1969 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Local 791, Lorbrook Co. and Textile By-Products, By-Laws, 1960; 1976; 1982 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Local 791, Lorbrook Co., Contracts (1 of 2), 1966-1990 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Local 791, Lorbrook Co., Contracts (2 of 2), 1966-1990 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Local 791, Minutes, 1951-1954; 1956-1966; 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Local 791, Textile By-Products, Contracts, 1957-1972 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Local 791, Textile By-Products Co. Textile By-Prods. vs. William Pollack, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Local 792, Bernhard Altman Int Corp., Contracts, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Local 792, Charter, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Local 792, High Rock Mills Inc, Contracts, 1955; 1956; 1959-1961 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Local 792, High Rock Mills Inc, Correspondence, 1956-1958 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Local 792, Philmont Finishing Co., Contracts, 1966-1968; 1970 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Local 835, Montco Corporation, Contract Negotiations, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Local 841, Berkshire Joint Board W.R. Grace, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Local 898, By-Laws, ca. 1965 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Local 898, French American British Woolens Corp, Contract, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Local 898, S. Stroock and Co., Arbitration, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Local 898, Stroock and Co., Contracts, 1956-1957; 1959-1960; 1962 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Local 898, S. Stroock and Co., Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Local 898, S. Stroock and Co., Employees' Handbook, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Local 898, S. Stroock and Co., Meeting Minutes, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Local 964, William Barnet & Son Inc, By-Laws, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Local 964, William Barnet & Son Inc, Contracts, 1961-1963; 1966-1967; 1969; 1971; 1973-1977 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Local 964, Meeting Minutes, 1960-1976 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Local 976, House of Montague and Stan Textile and Research, By-laws, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Local 976, Montague Upholstering Co., Contracts, 1964; 1966-1968; 1970; 1972; 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Local 976, Star Textile & Research Inc, Contracts, 1962-1985 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Local 982, Garnerville Holding Co., By-Laws, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Local 982, Garnerville Holding Company Inc., 1957-1982 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Local 982, Garnerville Holding Company, Membership Minutes, 1958-1960; 1962-1964 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Local 1001, I.M.I Wrap Knit, Arbitration, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Local 1001, I.M.I Wrap Knits, Contracts, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Local 1001, Leewin Fabrics, Contracts, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Local 1001, Minutes, 1952-1962 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Local 1001, Steinfield Fabrics, By-Laws, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Local 1001, Steinfields Fabrics Co., Contracts (1 of 2), 1959; 1961-1962; 1964-1970 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Local 1001, Steinfields Fabrics Co., Contracts (2 of 2), 1959; 1961-1962; 1964-1970 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Local 1032, By-Laws, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Local 1032, Correspondence, 1955; 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Local 1032, Minutes of Union Meetings, 1956-1958 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Local 1032, Printex Corporation, Arbitration, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Local 1032, Printex Corporation, By-Laws, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 38)